I'm fine.
I'm good.
Yeah.
So we have built a project where you can
learn things online very practically and
not in a very boring sense.
You can visualize things.
Yeah.
You can do things that are very boring in
nature, like reading PDS,
reading PPDS and not learning anything.
But you can learn things very practically
by visualization.
And our platform is providing you that
you you can upload a PDF for concepts you
want to learn and that will generate
images and visualization to understand
your problem and your concepts.
So shall we begin?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
So I have sent you one link in our chat
which is which is a pre quiz where you
can where you can do the opening or pre
quiz where you will learn things before
how you have learned that and after using
our platform how better you can answer
those questions.
You can open that link now.
OK, I can see the link.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So your voice is little bit breaking.
Can you hear me?
Hear me properly?
Yeah, I can hear you properly.
Can you hear me properly?
No.
Your voice is little bit breaking.
OK.
Hello.
Tell me.
Yeah, I can.
It gets better.
Hello.
It's better.
No problem.
OK.
So can you allow my name on my own or
would it be a interactive session?
You can directly answer those questions,
write your name,
and then try to answer the questions.
And then we can.
Yeah.
So do I.
Do you need the question out loud again?
No, you can.
No.
Yeah,
you can do it inside your mind and answer
them.
Question you do not have to like too much
worry about the questions and answers you
can direct,
you can just read and like answer them
whichever you feel right.
Sorry,
of course this quiz is read some biology
concept which I'm completely unaware of,
but I'll try, yeah.
If we do not know the answers,
we can completely skip it as well.
OK, Yeah, skip, skip, skip.
You can download that PDF and later share
it to me.
OK yeah I did clicked on the download but
nothing is seems to happening.
You have clicked download right?
Or you can print or save as a PDF.
OK,
I did click on that yet still nothing
seems still happens.
Oh it's not working.
No problem you can later you can keep
this tab and later send it to me.
OK gonna try one more right?
Are checking your folder what you can?
Can you one try one more time and check
in your folder like is it working or not?
I'm clicking both the buttons yet nothing
seems to pop up.
OK, don't worry.
No problem.
Now you can OK Or you can screenshot them
and later later send it to me.
3, 12 13 4.
OK.
And I think I'll take on the screen shot.
Yeah.
So I have sent you one more link,
which is our project.
And yeah, you can open that.
OK.
All right.
You can change it to English.
Yes, that took more preferable.
OK.
Yeah, yeah.
So, so is this is your project?
Yeah, you can.
On the far left side,
you can see the folder option where for
that.
OK, that's I said hierarchy.
OK, Yeah, you can.
Yeah, X you can see XR ID, Yeah.
And you can click the viruses.
OK, sample course,
ready to open wireless structure
classification.
Yeah, yeah.
Open ensemble course classification on
this music Alanka and courses what should
be located, right?
Yeah, yeah.
So this is the course.
You can read it and answer the questions
and if you have any without,
you can ask on the right side AIT
teaching agent and you can learn.
It can learn you from very basic to very
advanced like in a very great manner.
So you can do a start reading.
Yeah, yeah.
This is the AIT agent and this agent,
this is,
is this a more ask plan and agent?
Yeah, explains only.
Thanks directly.
OK, that's great.
All right.
And then you can ask after reading,
you can answer the follow up quiz and it
will show you it is right or wrong.
OK, OK,
not have to like study all all the
sections,
but really like how many you can do at A1
at one time.
No pressure.
But yeah,
do at least three sections from that.
OK, Yeah, yeah, I can do that.
Yeah.
So after reading that,
you can answer the follow up, please.
Sir, your voice is breaking.
Sorry.
In the follow up quiz.
In the follow up quiz there's a multiple
choice question,
yet I cannot choose the option as I
choose it.
It goes in the edit mode like how does
the size of variant compared to the
proprietor cell.
And I cannot choose the option as it goes
to.
And now I can write here.
I don't know how to do it.
Could you then please?
I'm not supposed to choose.
Yeah,
you can just click that and move forward.
Yeah.
Alright, hold on, I'll mark it.
So do I have?
Can you open this link into Chrome?
Is it your browser?
Nope,
I am currently working in the Chrome
browser.
OK, no problem.
I have write down your learning time at
OK 1012 or like how much time did it take
to learn the concepts?
I think there is a lot in the quiz and
students say so and itself.
Using what?
You just really explain what's wrong with
that idea and these options are missing.
Can you see it?
Yeah, the options correct?
Yep, the options are missing, no.
You can move forward though with another
concern, if you are, yeah.
It's the same whatever choice.
That's the options.
Maybe not obviously one or two multiply
the Y, not I Percent will not multiply,
it has no value.
Rejects 2 multiplies.
It means.
None.
Sorry for the disturbance,
but there is a very like voice cracking
noise so I cannot hear you properly if
you are saying anything.
No problem.
Yeah, yeah,
I think I have computed around 5 sections.
Can you go to the another section dial or
not?
OK,
that's one brilliant which I'm just and
so on.
Did you find it, like, good?
Like how you can separate those things
and learn it better?
Yeah, it's quite interactive.
And you can, yeah,
literally do the stuff on like in real
time.
If you are finished with that,
you can go to another section.
OK.
One to another vote for three would be
alright.
Hello.
Hello, can you hear me?
OK, you are done with that.
You can do the Start learning.
Click on the Start learning OK and you
can submit that now with your answer, OK.
OK, I think it's some sort of error.
No problem.
You, you, yeah,
you can exit the learning and yeah,
you can.
Or either you can ask AI about your about
your doubts from the chapter,
like in the right side.
Yeah, you can ask anything, please.
You can turn it into ask more not in the
agent tomorrow.
Juice even 5.
That's great.
Morocco Field.
Hello.
Yes, yes, yes.
What happened?
Yeah, No problem.
You can move forward.
I'm going to ask you some questions,
all right.
And yeah, so it's done in one sentence.
You can like tell me, let's before that,
let's do one thing that on your learning,
let's answer the quiz again and let's see,
is this really helpful to improve your
knowledge and learning experience?
Can we reopen the quiz?
OK.
Is it opening?
Yeah.
None.
Hello, I'm finished with the quiz.
Great.
Then can you download the answers now?
Yes, I have downloaded the answer.
Oh great.
Yeah.
So I want to ask you few little questions
like how was your experience before using
the like don't experience like your
learning stage and after learning from
our platform, is it worth it or not?
In one sentence, what you did you like?
What didn't you like?
Let's begin with how was your experience?
Yeah, I had a pretty decent experience.
I know the 1st and the 1st quiz I gave,
I actually did not have any idea about
the particular section of the subject,
tried some sort of reasoning with it,
having no idea.
And then I went to the platform where
they had a very structural way of putting
things, OK.
And it was really interruptive.
It's the visuals and the diagrams which
sort of helped me a lot to keep me
engaged rather than just the theory.
It was a great, yeah,
which was pretty great part and following
the section that was quiz in order to
create that particular section that we
have read.
So I found it really amusing and also
that the AI assistant feature was also
helpful.
You know,
anytime you're reading something and
something pops up in your head,
question something that's not written,
but you have it.
And sometimes it's it actually bothers
you.
So it's really pretty good to have a
assistant.
And, you know,
you guys are using clouds or top notch
models.
It's really impressive.
Yeah.
So I'll tell you what what is like,
how was the like speed,
how was the waiting or generation.
Or like was it interactive or not or
something like that.
I think the quiz section,
as a scope of improvement, I wouldn't say.
And the image quality is used.
They may get better if you can use some
other models.
And that's the input I can give you for
that.
Apart from it,
I think overall it was a good experience.
OK, So yeah, what did you like the most?
Like quiz section, interactive section,
3D generation.
Yeah, yeah,
3D generation was really something.
I would like to point out that, you know,
the section where I have to segregate
some of the traits to bacteria and the
virus,
that actually gave me a pretty good idea
about what is happening and what I'm
learning.
So that section really stand out.
OK,
so where did you like get frustrated and
what didn't you like?
OK, the follow up quiz section,
do I think underdeveloped because I had a
problem navigating through it.
Yeah, it's not most,
but for the most part I think it's a bit
technical issue rather than the
everything looks OK.
Yeah.
So did the course match the PDF or is it
too shallow about right or too much?
I think it's bit shallow.
You know, they,
they didn't go as deep or started with a
particular notch that they are teaching
it, focusing on a particular section.
But that's more of a structural part,
I guess.
Yeah.
Would you use this tool for your own
studying or for teaching someone else?
Yeah,
If I have a particular access on the
structure side,
I would really use it in order to teach
it.
But as far as I go,
or would I use it for my own study?
Depends on the material fairly.
But if I have to use it as a machine or
tool,
so I could teach somebody and then I I
have a control over the structure
materials.
Yeah, I think I would use it.
OK, one more thing,
like if we could fix only one thing,
what should it be?
One thing in technical terms,
I think the website deals with congested.
You can, yeah,
definitely do some work on the UI.
You can hide the AI teaching agent as
well and outline as well if you just want
to study the stuff like in the center
part.
Yep.
Apart from that you you can download our
transcript and save that as well.
Those are the added feature in that, no,
from my suggestion,
even if I remove the bolts in order to be
more interactive or something of a really
engaging the fonts and the backgrounds,
I think the UI needs a work in order to
be more interactive.
That's all.
Apart from that, I think as a basic the,
you know, the prototype,
it's it looks pretty good.
Yeah.
Thank you.
And lastly,
anything else you want to tell us?
Oh, I think that's all I had to say.
Really good experience.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you for your time, Kirzan.
It was a pleasure talking with you.
And thank you for the feedback to improve
our website and learning experience for
everyone.
We will definitely improve this
experience.
We are still learning and improving our
website and you are one of the first,
you are the first member to review our
website and use that.
Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
Yeah, the best for your website.
I hope you guys do well.
Thank you.
Yeah, Yeah.
Krishna postcard there.